[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[In my prime]
[Episode 17]
Sweetie,
you finally called me.
I knew it.
My hunch is always right.
Did you eat your birthday cake?
And the fried mushrooms,
the buns and all that—
did they get to you?
Dad,
it's my birthday.
I'm not gonna shortchange myself.
I ordered a huge bowl
of thick‑cut noodles
with lots of meat in it.
See? I'm eating right now.
It's very chewy.
Next time you come to Haizhou,
I'll bring you here to try it.
Good, as long as you're eating well.
Your mom
worries about you out there alone,
not eating properly.
And about the address.
Dad, I moved to a new place.
Yeah, I didn't like
the place I lived in before.
You know, I've made some money,
so I'm thinking of moving
to a place with a better environment.
Tell uncle to take
the buns and mushrooms back.
I don't have a fridge
where I live right now,
so I can't keep them.
Really?
Okay.
Have you settled in yet?
Don't forget to send me your new address.
Living alone in a new city,
you've got to stay safe.
Just make sure
I can reach you if something comes up.
I know, Dad. Don't worry.
Ma'am,
I didn't order a poached egg.
The table over there
ordered it for you just now.
He said it's not easy for a young girl
to be away from home,
and wished you a happy birthday.
I'm sorry.
You didn't react just now,
so I got curious
what you were listening to.
Just randomly listening.
[Fundamentals of Mechanical Engineering]
[Mechanical Engineering Drawing]
Aren't you a finance major?
Why are you reading these?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I was counting my steps
and didn't notice.
One of your strides
is about two of mine.
I was just testing that.
Okay.
I figured someone
as impressive as you
would be listening to English
wherever you go,
killing it in extracurriculars
like swimming and basketball,
and probably playing an instrument too.
That's not me you're describing.
I noticed.
It really isn't you.
In the library,
you read books from other majors,
and listen to the theme songs
of idol dramas.
Cao Xin,
you're very different
from what I imagined.
I originally wanted to major
in mechanical engineering,
but my family wouldn't let me.
Well, you could switch majors
for grad school.
I haven't decided if I'll go
to grad school yet.
If you make up your mind,
you can come to me.
Come to you?
I'm planning to study abroad
for my master's.
But
I lack self-discipline.
I need a study buddy.
Okay.
I have class later. Gotta go.
Remember to come to me.
You really want to work for me?
You're a college student.
You could do anything.
Even just dating.
I'm just working to pay my tuition.
You know what
my family's situation is.
Besides,
didn't we agree?
When you're the boss,
you have to hire me.
All right, Zhang.
Even though
I'm also
barely scraping by,
since you're with me now,
we start with a street stall.
Every penny counts.
I won't let you work for nothing.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Hang the lights, open for business.
Okay.
-Come check it out!
-Authentic export surplus!
The latest styles!
Factory clearance, export surplus!
Our clothes' quality is unmatched—
all export surplus.
Look.
Is this really export surplus?
Yes.
Why are the tags still attached?
Let me tell you.
Here's the thing.
These clothes were all custom orders
from foreigners.
We've got serious connections
with the factory
to score this batch.
Definitely authentic export surplus.
See? Look at this.
The tag's cut off.
With this quality,
it'll easily last you three years.
Ladies,
looking for authentic export surplus?
New store opening!
Ladies, come support us!
Authentic export surplus!
Come take a look!
Ladies,
check out our clothes.
Look at this great quality.
Come take a look!
Come check it out!
Authentic export surplus!
New store opening!
Buy more, save more!
Ladies, see anything you like?
This is 20 yuan.
I'll give you 20% off if you buy it.
How about it?
Thirty yuan.
Forty yuan.
Fifty yuan.
Miss, how about taking a dress?
I'll give you 20% off
if you take it.
City inspectors!
Hurry, hurry!
City inspectors.
Sorry.
What do we do with the clothes?
Carry them and run!
I...
City inspectors!
Miss, give me five minutes.
Wait for me!
Five minutes!
I'll be right back,
just taking a quick lap!
Stop!
Oh my god!
What a—what a—
What a coincidence, Sir.
Not a coincidence at all.
I've been waiting here for you.
According to Article 18,
Paragraph 2
of the Haizhou City Regulations
on Appearance
and Environmental Sanitation...
Captain.
Got her.
No, no, no. Sir.
This is my first offense.
First offense, let me go.
Please?
What if I catch you again?
I've run into you so many times.
How about this?
I'll run faster next time...
Stop!
Stop! You two—follow!
Back alley!
Turn right!
I'm telling you...
Don't run!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Sir, here's a gift for you.
Wear it, your date will go great!
This kid...
Sir, give me one of these.
Okay.
You've kept this chocolate
for a long time.
Don't let it go bad.
How about you let me eat it?
It won't go bad.
It'll just melt
into a sticky gooey mess,
still tastes good though.
Back in high‑school,
Zhi always brought me some.
For the longest time
I thought
good chocolate
was supposed to turn into sticky goop.
So you prepared this
for Qi Zhi?
I want to go see him
when I settle down.
Hello?
Hello.
This is Nanqing County Prison.
Your visitation request
has been denied.
The inmate refuses
to accept visitors.
Why?
The inmate
didn't give a clear explanation.
But our principle is
to respect his wishes.
Then can I send him some chocolate?
We provide
all the basic daily necessities here.
We don't accept packages.
Alright.
Sorry for the trouble. Thank you.
You can eat it.
Don't let it go bad.
Not afraid it'll go bad?
Then I won't hold back.
How much is this shirt?
Thirty-five yuan each.
If you buy more,
I can give you a discount.
Let me see.
This one.
This one's perfect for this weather.
Can I try it on?
Sure, go ahead.
Ma'am, a newspaper, please.
Still won't see us?
Okay.
Thank you.
Sorry for the trouble.
Okay, okay.
Okay, bye.
He still won't see us.
If he won't see us, so be it.
I think this kid has made up his mind.
We won't apply
and won't go see him.
Shi also tried to visit,
but he turned her away too.
He won't even see his sister?
You know,
these two kids are both so headstrong.
When they were little,
Shi would call me "Mom"
a hundred times a day.
Now that she's grown up,
she's flown the coop.
And I, her own mother,
am less than a stranger.
Don't put it that way.
It's a good thing
that kids have their own ideas.
It just shows they're considerate,
letting us worry less.
Worry less?
Which one of them
has ever made us worry less?
Which one has ever been easy?
No.
I need to get through
to at least one of them.
Aren't you going to Haizhou tomorrow
to stock up?
Go visit Qi Shi.
See where she is
and what big company she's in.
I just don't buy it.
See how she's really doing.
If she's struggling,
bring her home.
Why don't you come with me?
If I go, who's gonna watch the shop?
Besides, stocking up—
isn't that
you men's business?
Don't try to dump it on me.
Okay.
I'll go see our girl,
then I'll let you know she's okay.
The main thing is stocking up.
Okay, fine.
Come on,
check out my newly upgraded gear.
How is it?
Buy on the go,
carry it with you,
sell it as you go.
Just set up the grill.
Not bad.
Right?
If I were the strict inspector,
I couldn't find a single fault.
I'm just gonna...
make a run for it.
Careful, don't spill that.
Yeah, I gotta...
Plant my feet firmly,
and start grilling.
Hello, how much is this shirt?
Feel free to look.
Let me tell you,
in the building next door,
they charge over 100 yuan for this.
Here, it's only 20 yuan.
Alright, I'll keep looking.
[Dad]
Tired from work every day?
Get some lamb skewers! Skewers!
W‑What's wrong?
Why are you so nervous?
No—no one. It's nothing.
Here.
Dad, I'm in a meeting.
I can't talk right now.
Tired from work every day?
Get some lamb skewers,
something different.
Sweetie,
I'm in Haizhou.
When do you get off work?
Authentic charcoal-grilled lamb skewers!
Wang,
keep it down.
Okay, okay.
Try a skewer.
Fresh off the grill.
Hello?
Hello, Dad.
Why didn't you
tell me you were coming?
I'm in a meeting at work.
It's fine.
Your mom misses you,
so she asked me to come check on you.
What time do you get off work?
How about I go wait for you
at your workplace?
No, no, no.
Hello, how is this dress...
No.
What's with that attitude?
No, Dad.
Dad, Dad.
Our company
has super‑strict confidentiality rules.
And...
there's nowhere to sit at the entrance.
You'd have no place to hang out.
How about this:
I'm working really late today,
so you go back first.
Next time, let me know before you come,
then I'll
go pick you up at the station.
It's fine.
I'll do as you say.
Right, right. My boss is calling me.
I gotta go.
I'm coming back to Haizhou for May Day.
Sure, that's great.
Hurry back.
Everyone back home is waiting for you.
Then you'd better host us well.
I'm not coming alone.
Not alone?
Does that mean you have a girlfriend?
Good for you, man.
I'm gonna
hype this up
in our class group chat later.
The class monitor is returning home
in glory with his family.
It's my school's debate team,
an off-campus event.
Five or six people.
Forget five or six,
even ten or twenty,
I can afford to host them.
If it comes down to it,
I'll ask Qi Shi and the others to join us.
Qi Shi?
Did you get in touch with her?
I didn't.
But Fatty is in touch with her.
We can take this opportunity
to have a get-together.
Mind if I sit here?
What's that voice?
I think I just heard
a beautiful girl's voice.
Bye.
On the phone with a friend?
My high school classmate.
Remember we're going
to Haizhou for May Day?
I was just telling him.
If he's free,
we can all hang out.
Sure.
It'd be great to have a local guide.
Does that mean we can meet
that good neighbor you mentioned?
Her...
We haven't been in touch for a long time.
I don't even know if I can reach her.
Don't you have her phone number?
No.
What about QQ?
I have her QQ.
Then you can reach her.
Just leave her a message on QQ.
She hasn't logged into QQ
in a long time.
Cao Xin,
where there's a will, there's a way.
You're right.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
Let's go to the library
after we eat.
Didn't you say
you needed a study buddy?
Exams are coming up.
Time for some last‑minute cramming.
Okay.
Big news.
Class Monitor Cao has a girlfriend.
Check the class group chat.
Stop spreading rumors.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Come on.
I swear I heard
a girl having dinner with you.
Nothing left?
Nope.
I'm locking up now.
What is this?
Don't take random unknown stuff.
Toss it out.
Wait, wait, wait.
What is it?
Look at what it says on the package.
Specialty pastries from Beining.
Cao Xin sent these over?
Cao Xin,
Mrs. Huo really loves
those pastries you sent.
She kept saying how delicious they were.
Next time I don't have class,
I'll bring my roommates over
to support your business.
Sure.
Your roommates will get
VIP treatment—10 % off.
No, 20% off.
Ask them
what styles they like,
and I'll stock up in advance
so they don't make a wasted trip.
Sure thing, Boss Qi.
How does that saying go?
"Whatever you do, do it well."
You really figured out
the tricks of the trade.
You bet.
I'm gonna be
the Warren Buffett of street stalls.
Still going on
about Buffett after all these years?
Can't let go of that dream.
Right.
Cao Xin asked me for your number.
He wanted us all to get together
in Haizhou during the next long holiday.
I'm not going.
Nothing to see him about.
Cao Xin.
Speak of the devil and he shall appear.
Why aren't you answering?
What would I even say?
That I'm running a street stall
and don't have time?
That Qi Shi, who used to compete with him
for first place in everything,
has been reduced to a street vendor.
He would laugh his head off at me.
Cao Xin can be
quite sharp-tongued sometimes.
I remember you two
drawing an imaginary line
down the middle of your desks
all through school.
You were either competing over grades
or fighting for
the class monitor position.
Our homeroom teacher even said
you two would even argue over
whether an ant was male or female
if one walked past.
Yeah.
Back then,
no matter what it was,
I always had the upper hand over him.
It's different now.
The tables have turned.
I can't even hold a candle to him.
I understand.
If I were you,
I'd struggle with that gap too.
You two keep talking about Cao Xin.
Who is Cao Xin?
Your boyfriend?
No, no, no.
Don't...
Don't buy this in the future.
It can't even hold the clothes.
But someone did come
looking for you this morning.
Must've been Cao Xin.
Was it a tall,
thin guy?
City inspectors!
You grab the cart. I'll grab the clothes.
-Hurry up.
-Okay.
See you at the usual spot.
Okay.
Stop right there!
Stop!
Stop! Don't run!
Don't run!
Stop!
Stop! Don't run!
Don't move! Stop!
Don't move!
Who? Who is it? Who?
Stop! Don't run!
Stop!
Dad?
Here.
What are you doing here?
Pretty impressive, huh?
Who else could it be?
Let's go.
Dad,
give them to me.
Sweetie,
why are you living in a basement?
It looks like a doghouse.
It depends on where the doghouse is.
Dad, look.
This is
a downtown basement.
That's different.
I worked hard to rent it.
Is it safe here?
Yes.
Dad,
I'm telling you, this place
is perfect for me.
Look,
there's no direct sunlight.
And
I have a fan.
I don't even need to buy
an air conditioner in summer.
It stays naturally cool.
A fan is enough.
It saves money.
Dad,
I told you
over the phone
that I left a big company
for something better.
I
really do feel like
I got something better.
Stop looking around, Dad.
I'll get you something to eat.
Dad,
the BBQ stand upstairs is pretty good.
Let me treat you.
No need.
Let's just make do.
You have steamed buns here.
With some soybean paste,
it's enough.
Here.
Hey, Sweetie,
why does your steamed bun
taste a bit
like spicy and sour shredded potatoes?
Sour?
Could it be spoiled?
Smell it.
Let me taste it again.
No, no,
it's not spoiled.
It's fine.
I've got it.
It tastes a little
like sweet and sour fish.
Great. It's not spoiled.
It really does
have a meaty aroma.
Crispy on the outside,
tender on the inside.
And no bones.
Delicious.
Let me try mine.
Let me see.
Spicy crayfish.
Try it again.
It also tastes
a bit like braised pork.
Alright.
We've got fish, meat, and crayfish
all in one.
Sweetie,
even though
you're going through some hard times now,
the taste of life
is just like this steamed bun.
♪ The wind blows my hair apart ♪
If you say it's sweet and sour fish,
then it's sweet and sour fish.
If you say it's spicy crayfish,
then it's spicy crayfish.
♪ The story slowly gets complicated too ♪
So,
how you want to live your life
is entirely up to you.
♪ We never became anyone's myth ♪
Right?
♪ Only learned to grow up in the rain ♪
Sweetie,
I know you're feeling wronged.
♪ Should we blame fate? ♪
You used to be number one,
and now
♪ Adulthood is bandaging your own falls ♪
you're setting up a street stall.
It doesn't sound good when people ask.
♪ Rented room, last bus ♪
♪ Where's the future? ♪
♪ How long since I dared
to say I'm scared ♪
But it's okay.
It's okay, sweetie.
I believe in you.
Who are you?
♪ We have nothing,
yet still we rush about ♪
You're my daughter, Qi Aihua's kid,
right?
There are no cowards
♪ Because you're here, there's an answer ♪
in our Qi family.
It's okay.
♪ Past dreams covered in dust ♪
Besides,
♪ It doesn't matter ♪
don't look down on running a street stall.
What's wrong with it?
♪ Some things just have to
be this way for now ♪
You running a stall—
that's following
in your old man's footsteps.
You know?
Let me tell you,
back when I got laid off,
I thought it was over.
The sky was falling.
But guess what?
I supported our whole family
by running a street stall.
Plenty of big shots
started out with street stalls.
Like who?
That customer of mine—Mr. Chen.
Mr. Chen. You know?
Mr. Chen.
Do you know what he used to do?
♪ The world spins too fast,
who hasn't panicked? ♪
No.
He rode a tricycle to sell tofu pudding.
♪ All I see is your gaze ♪
♪ If tomorrow there's nothing left ♪
♪ I'll still walk you home ♪
You're back.
Alright.
Now that I've seen you,
I can rest easy.
Your mom—
after all these years, you know her.
Sharp tongue, soft heart.
But deep down,
she's always been thinking about you.
Dad,
about me running the street stall—
can you help me
keep it from Mom for now?
What?
Afraid she won't approve?
When has she ever approved
of anything I do?
It's just that
I haven't made anything of myself yet.
I can't face her like this.
Sweetie,
she's your mom.
It's exactly because she's my mom
that I don't want her
to see me like this.
From the day I left home,
I swore
that the next time I see you guys,
I'd be decent
and successful.
Okay,
I respect your decision.
But you have to promise me something.
From now on, whatever comes up,
don't always grit your teeth
and bear it alone,
okay?
In our family,
I will always have your back,
got it?
Alright, hurry back now.
I'll come see you when I can.
Yeah, right here.
How is it?
Our botanical garden in Haizhou
is beautiful, isn't it?
It's beautiful.
Really beautiful.
The flowers are pretty too.
The flowers blooming
over there are so pretty.
To the left is Wild Duck Lake.
Up ahead there are a few
landmark buildings.
They're all free to visit,
so you can go check them out.
Which one do you want to hit first?
Wild Duck Lake.
Let's go to Wild Duck Lake first.
Alright, off to Wild Duck Lake.
What are you doing?
What?
I called Qi Shi, but she didn't answer.
You give her a call.
What's the rush?
Call her later.
Hurry up.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll call, I'll call.
But let's be clear—I'm only calling once.
I don't care if she answers or not.
She didn't answer you.
You really think she'd answer me?
Hello?
She answered.
What should I say?
Um, Qi Shi...
Tianji?
What are you up to?
I'm in Haizhou.
Are you busy?
Let's get together.
I'm quite busy. I don't have time.
Cao Xin,
aren't you guys going over?
Wait a moment.
She hung up.
Shoot, you got found out.
She heard your name.
Well.
Let's go check out Wild Duck Lake first.
What?
Nothing, nothing.
She's calling back.
Hello, Qi Shi.
Hello, Tianji.
I missed you so much.
I really want to hang out with you,
just the two of us.
Too bad I'm so busy,
no time.
I'm working
at a Fortune 500 company here.
Because of my outstanding performance,
my boss handpicked me
for a business trip to the US.
There's a whole Pacific Ocean
between us right now.
You wouldn't even see me
if I waved at you.
Working hard every day?
Have some lamb skewers to recharge!
Tired from work every day?
Come try some lamb skewers!
I'm going into a meeting.
Um,
I'm busy, gotta go.
Hello? Hello?
Lamb skewers?
Do Americans eat lamb skewers too?
Chinatown.
I don't know
if Americans eat lamb skewers,
but I suddenly
really want some right now.
I'm hungry too.
Where in Haizhou
has the best lamb skewers?
You should've said so earlier.
I'll take you to Haizhou's
biggest night market.
Let's go check out Wild Duck Lake first.
The air is so fresh.
I'm telling you,
I've been watching for days.
Because my accounts don't add up.
Either rolls of paper towels go missing,
or a few bottles of hand soap.
Stuff like bean paste
and salted duck eggs
disappear even faster.
One day takes the cake.
I had leftover fried dough sticks
and vegetable turnovers
in the morning,
planning to eat them for dinner.
But
the thief stole every last bit of it.
I mean,
it's not like they were stealing
anything expensive,
but it's just so annoying.
That thief really knows how to live
on a budget.
Honey, honey, it's me.
Me.
What the hell are you doing?
Well, the place was
such a mess,
so I tidied it up a little.
These things...
Qi Aihua,
are you seeing another woman?
Who? Me?
No.
Tell me the truth.
Are you seeing someone?
Don't accuse me wrongly.
How could that be?
Then who are
all these things for?
No,
nothing like that, I...
Qi Aihua,
you're really something, aren't you?
Old as you are,
but full of dirty tricks.
-What are you doing?
-Don't move!
What are you talking about?
Don't move.
Let go of your hands.
What do you think I'm talking about?
What are you doing?
I'm looking for evidence.
It's not what you think.
Not what you think.
You old fool, you...
These are for a girl.
These are for our daughter.
Is she only
your daughter?
Do you have to be
so sneaky
about giving her things?
Besides,
doesn't she work at a big company?
You...
Do you really need to bring her
all this random stuff,
this junk?
Who'd even want this?
I'll tell you the truth.
She never worked at a big company.
She's running a street stall
selling clothes.
Guys,
this is the biggest
local night market.
Taking our top scholar Cao
to the night market.
Hope anyone nearby
gets a chance to spot us.
Pick up the phone.
Just came in today.
You can
take two pieces,
and I'll give you a discount.
Okay. Thank you.
Come back anytime.
Okay.
Cao Xin is at the night market.
Quick, hide.
Ma'am,
look, my daughter
tried this on at home
and it's a bit small.
Could I exchange it
for one size up?
I'll exchange it for you.
How about this one?
Great.
Wang.
My stomach hurts.
Watch the stall for me.
Okay, okay, okay.
Wrong again.
I need a bigger size.
This is exactly the same.
Find it yourself.
They're all here.
Ma'am, it's fine.
They're all right here.
Just look through them yourself.
Tianji, is the pineapple good?
It's good. Very sweet.
This vendor has pretty good taste.
Does this look good?
Working hard every day?
Have some lamb skewers to recharge!
Tired from work every day?
Come try some lamb skewers!
Is the owner
of this stall a young girl?
Yes.
What's her name then?
Qi Shi.
Eat while it's hot.
Thanks.
Try it.
Didn't find her?
The stall next door said
this stall belongs to Qi Shi.
If you want to see her,
we can wait a bit longer,
or come back tomorrow.
Let's go.
Where is my ID card?
I put it right in this bag.
Why is it gone?
If you can't find it, just let it be.
It's so late,
and I'm hungry.
Honey, cook some noodles.
Make it yourself.
I can't wait another minute.
The bus to Haizhou's long gone.
And even if you went,
you'd need your ID to stay at a hotel.
How's that gonna help you
make up with our daughter?
Was it you?
What?
Did you hide
my ID card?
I didn't.
Give it to me.
I didn't take your ID card.
You just wanna stop me
from seeing our daughter.
I don't.
You...
Fine, Qi Aihua, you...
You and our daughter,
you two are totally in cahoots,
sneaking around,
and plotting behind my back.
You can't stop me, you...